Obviously the question of what math actually is,
has been debated for much of history.
And due to Godel's incompleteness theorems,
there is no objective answer.
If we visualize the totality of math as a
set, then its border cannot be clearly defined.
Note that we can either choose to visualize
the totality of math syntactically or semantically.
Syntactically this would be the set of all
true mathematical formulas written in first order logic,
and semantically would be the totality of mathematical structures.
Where mathematical structures can be seen as pre-existing eternal
objects in a platonic world of forms.